proxyclick.com 2015-05-12

# Privacy Policy

### Your privacy is critically important to us. The data remains yours, after all!

We like to provide you with a personalised web service, which makes it necessary for us to hold and process your personal information. According to the legal definition, personal data is every data that allows the identification of a natural person. It is sufficient that the data allow us to establish a (direct or indirect) link between one or more data pieces and a natural person.

At Proxyclick, we are committed to making sure that your personal information is kept confidential, and that it is only used for those specific purposes that are in-line with Proxyclick’s mission to assist you with Visitor Management and/or your facility-related service requests (Service Desk). We are convinced that such privacy policy is essential to creating confidence, goodwill and stronger relationships with you, our customers. That is why we inform you in the most extensive manner about the collecting and processing of your personal data. Therefore, you will always be aware of the type, the extent of, and the purposes for which personal data are collected and used.

By providing you this information, we confirm our compliance with the most important strict legislative conditions as required by the Belgian data protection legislation – in particular, the Act of 8 December 1992 on Privacy Protection in relation to the Processing of Personal Data (Privacy Act), which implemented the EU Data Protection Directive 95/46 EC.

We assume that the user of our applications has taken notice of this Privacy Policy and agreed to the collection and processing of personal information that are in accordance thereto. Be aware that we do occasionally update this Privacy Policy, and that it is your responsibility to examine and take notification of any change made to this document. So please do return and review this Policy on a regular basis. Any substantial change will be clearly communicated.

If you still have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please do not hesitate to contact us at info@proxyclick.com. We’d love to hear your feedback.

**1\. Who is responsible for the data processing?**

The Privacy Act draws a distinction between a ‘data controller’ and a ‘data processor’. We provide you with a clear notice of this distinction, as this is extremely important to avoid some ambiguity about responsibilities.

**Data Controller**

The data controller is every natural person and/or legal entity that determines the purposes and the means (legal and technical) of the processing of personal data. This determination can be done alone or jointly with others.

The data controller behind ‘Visitor Management’ and ‘Service Desk’ is:

_PROXYCLICK sprl_  
 _Rue Fernand Bernier 15_  
_B-1060 Brussels_  
 _Belgium_  
 _Registration Number: BE0863.261.693_  
 _Tel:+32 25 43 44 23_  
_Email:[info@proxyclick.com](mailto:info@proxyclick.com)_

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems. Furthermore, we are always ready to perform audits on request.

Be aware that Proxyclick is only the data controller for what is provided underneath. You are the one assuming responsibility for the personal data of third parties you published or shared through our application, including those of your visitors. You declare to have the right to communicate or display them, thus relieving the data controller of all responsibility. Regarding these data, Proxyclick only acts as actual processor.

**Data Processors**

Proxyclick uses a number of online data processors that collect, store and process your data. These data processors are natural persons or legal entities that process the personal data on behalf of the data controller Proxyclick.The personswho, under the direct authority of the party responsible for the processing, are authorised to process the data do not fall within this category.

We have carefully selected these processors, which are fully listed in Section 6. The selected processors offer notably all the adequate guarantees with regard to technical and organizational security measures taken as to the processing of your personal data. They also satisfy all the other requirements of Article 16, §1 of the Privacy Act.

The controller is not responsible for any loss or corruption of personal data, identity theft, data theft, viruses or Trojans, SQL injections or other attacks on computer systems or online cloud portals. The processors have gained professional expertise in their domain and therefore decide in an autonomous manner the most technically appropriate application to process the data. The data controller is not expected to have the same expertise and specialty.

**2\. What information do we collect about you?**

We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal information:

  * Information about your computer such as hardware and software, and about your visits to and use of this website (including your IP address, geographical location, operating system and browser type).
  * Information that you provide to us for the purpose of registration, which is required to obtain access to the application (Visitor Management or Service Desk). The registration requires you to provide us with personal contact information, such as your name, company name and email address, and to select a password. In addition, upon the purchase of a subscription, we also require certain financial information, which we will not have access to as it will be managed by payment providers
  * Any other information that you choose to send to us, such as when you contact us with inquiries.

Dependent on whether the user makes intensive use of the website or relies on certain services, the collection of personal data may be more extensive.

The website also collects anonymous data, which is corresponding technical data that is used solely for internal purposes to get information on user navigation. Since these data are not used to identify users, they do fall outside this Privacy Statement.

**3\. For what purposes do we process the data?**

We process your personal information for an overarching goal: we want to offer you the best-personalised experience when visiting our website and using our applications.

The information we collect about you is primarily processed to help us ensure the user the proper technical functioning of the website and to provide you access to the application in a secure, effective and user-related manner. Our aim is to provide you with the best possible services. We need your information in order to better understand how you access and use our website and services, to then be able to improve them and respond to your wishes, questions and criticisms.

We would like to offer our services in the most efficient and personalised way. This implies that we may use your personal information to tailor the content we send or display to you, to offer location customization, and personalized help and instructions, and to otherwise personalize your experiences while using the website or our services.

We may also use your information internally for marketing and promotional purposes. For example, we may use it to send you news and newsletters, special offers, and promotions, or to otherwise contact you about products or information we think may interest you. You can always unsubscribe from such e-mails.

The way we offer you the application and its related services remains subject to constant changes, as we are still evolving. It is therefore important that you give us permission to use your personal information in a manner that allows us to develop new innovative features and services. These new developments remain within our original objectives.

**4\. How long will we hold your data?**

We only process your personal information as long as necessary. We do keep a record of your data as long as your account is active, or if your personal data is necessary to offer you a particular service. We promise to delete your personal data as soon as this data is no longer required for the aforementioned purposes. The deletion is comparable to deleting files on your computer using the ‘trash bin’, allowing us to recover the data to a certain extent for some time.

**5\. Where do we store your information and that of your visitors?**

We store all the personal information you provide in a database on several servers, hosted in France via OVH.OVH’s General Terms and Conditions of Service are available via the following link: <http://www.ovh.com/us/support/termsofservice/General_Terms_of_Service_US.pdf>.

We use iBackup as our secondary back-up provider. A full back-up of our practice database files is transferred to iBackup once every 24 hours. iBackup’s Privacy Policy is available at <https://www.ibackup.com/policy_new.htm>.

**6.** **Do we share your information?**

We, at Proxyclick, consider mutual confidence very important. That’s why we would like to ensure you that we process your personal information only for internal use. We neither rent nor sell your personal information or that of your visitors in personally identifiable form to anyone but the trusted and reputable third party processors listed hereunder.

To help us deliver our Service, we use various third party applications:

**We want to make sure our website is optimal and for that we need analytics and insight.** **We use the following third-party web analytics services to help us understand your usage of our website and services and improve your user experience:**

  * Google Analytics

_We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users’ computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information._ _At no point does Google store personal information; it only stores anonymous data such as connection time, device used, and location._

_Google’s Privacy Policy is available at_[ _http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html_](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html) _._

  * HubSpot

_We use HubSpot_ _to connect with our already active clients, as well as to reach out to inactive clients_ _and candidates in the hopes of sparking new successful business relationships. HubSpot is a tool that enables us to_ _enhance how we communicate with our customers and, more broadly, our visitors_ _. HubSpot_ _complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework, as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of personal information from European Union member countries._ _HubSpot has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles_ _of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement._

_For more information about HubSpot’s Privacy Policy, go to:_[ _http://www.hubspot.com/legal/privacy-policy_](https://www.hubspot.com/legal/privacy-policy) _._

  * Intercom

_Intercom analyzes your use of our website and/or product and tracks our relationship so that we can improve our service to you. We may also use Intercom as a medium for communications, either through email or through messages within our product(s). As part of our service agreements, Intercom collects publicly available contact and social information related to you, such as your email address, gender, company, job title, photos, website URLs, social network handles and physical location, to enhance your user experience._

_For more information on the privacy practices of Intercom, please visit_[ _http://docs.intercom.io/privacy_](http://docs.intercom.io/privacy) _._ _Intercom’s services are governed by Intercom’s terms of use, which can be found at_[ _http://docs.intercom.io/terms_](http://docs.intercom.io/terms) _. If you would like to opt out of having this information collected by or submitted to Intercom, please_[ _contact us_](mailto:support@teambookapp.com) _._

**We use the following third-party online billing platform to simplify the billing process:**

  * ChargeBee

_A copy of its Privacy Policy is available at_[ _https://www.chargebee.com/privacy.html_](https://www.chargebee.com/privacy.html) _._

_They will save credit card details at their PCI compliant gateway interface partner Spreedly (<https://spreedly.com/pci>)._

**We use the following third-party payment services provider to track and manage new customers’ inquiries:**

  * Ingenico Payment Services (ex-Ogone)

_Ingenico Payment Services, previously Ogone, is a leading global digital payment service provider that turns complex financial transactions into seamless payment solutions. A copy of its Privacy Policy can be found at_[ _http://payment-services.ingenico.com/be/en/cookie-policy_](http://payment-services.ingenico.com/be/en/cookie-policy) _._

_This provider will save credit card details and is PCI-compliant._

**We use the following third-party CRM to track and manage new customers enquires:**

  * Salesforce

_When you sign up for our services, we will share account information as necessary for Salesforce to_ _provide that service. You can find its Privacy Policy at:_[ _http://www.salesforce.com/company/privacy/_](http://www.salesforce.com/company/privacy/) _._

**We use the following third-party** **live chatting solution** **in order to offer you a website chat:**

  * SnapEngage

_SnapEngage enables a direct contact with our company. In order to establish contact with you via SnapEngage, SnapEngage requires your email address. SnapEngage uses cookies, which allow for an analysis of how you use our web pages. The information about your use of our web pages generated by the cookies are transferred to the server of SnapEngage in the United States of America on our behalf and stored there. SnapEngage uses the information on our behalf in order to analyze your use of our web pages and to provide a chat window on our web pages through which you can directly contact us. You can find further information about SnapEngage and the use of your data at SnapEngage at_ [_http://snapengage.com/privacy-policy/_](http://snapengage.com/privacy-policy/).

We carefully selected these external service providers and review them regularly to ensure that your privacy is preserved. All such third party processors are contractually bound by us to keep your information confidential. All information provided to third party processors is used by them only to carry out the service they are providing for us.

We will not transfer your data to any other third parties without letting you know in advance or asking for your prior permission. We may only transfer your data to other third parties without informing you separately beforehand in the exceptional cases legally provided for in the Privacy Act, notably when such transfer is necessary or legally required on important public interest grounds, or for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims.

In order to further develop our business, we may alter the corporate structure of Proxyclick by changing its legal form. We may also form, sell or buy subsidiaries, divisions or parts of the company. In such transactions, customer information, together with the part of the company to be transferred, will be passed on. Every time personal data are transferred to third parties to the extent prescribed, Proxyclick will ensure that this is done in accordance with this Privacy Policy and the relevant data protection laws.

Proxyclick is a Belgian company but operates globally. It is therefore possible for the data to be transferred to and stored in countries outside the European Economic Area. However, Proxyclick will always do so in accordance with this Privacy Policy and applicable laws.

**7\. What are my rights as a data subject?**

Each user can be assured that his personal data will be processed in a fair and lawfully manner. This means that the data will only be processed for the above explicit and legitimate purposes. Proxyclick also ensures that the personal data are always adequate, relevant and not excessive in relation to the purposes for which they are processed.

**Right to Access**

Each user who proves his identity has a right of access to all information regarding the processing of his personal data by Proxyclick, as defined in the Privacy Act. This includes information on the purposes of the processing, the categories of information processed and the categories of recipients to whom the data are provided. This Privacy Policy is a first indication.

The user shall exercise his right through a signed, written request to Proxyclick, by post or e-mail to info@proxyclick.com. Proxyclick undertakes the appropriate action following a request within 15 days.

**Right to Correct**

Proxyclick attaches a great importance to an accurate data collection. Inaccurate or incomplete personal data can therefore always be improved or even obliterated.

As it is impossible for us to be aware of any mistakes, incompleteness or falseness of your personal data on a continuous basis, it is up to you as a user to report inaccuracies or omissions and to perform the necessary adjustments regarding one’s registration details.

If your personal actions seem inadequate, feel free to contact us using a signed, written request directed at [info@proxyclick.com](mailto:info@proxyclick.be). Proxyclick performs the necessary actions within 15 days by making additions, correcting or deleting the personal data. The removal is mainly related to the visibility, so it is possible that the deleted personal data remains temporarily stored.

**Right to Object**

Each user can oppose the processing of his personal data. This right to object exists only if there are sufficient legitimate and weighty grounds relating to his particular situation. The exceptions provided in the Privacy Act are also applicable to this right of objection.You may at any time, free of charge and without further ado, oppose the proposed processing of your personal data if those data were obtained for the purpose of direct marketing.

You are also entitled to obtain the removal of and/or the ban on the use of all your personal data, which have been obtained and which are incomplete or irrelevant, regarded from the view of the purpose of the processing. This is also applicable to any personal data of which the registration, disclosure, and retention are prohibited, or personal data preserved after expiry of the authorized period. This right can be used at any time, free of charge and without further justification.

You shall exercise this right through a signed, written request to Proxyclick, by post or e-mail to info@proxyclick.com. Proxyclick undertakes the appropriate action following a request within 15 days.

**8\. Do we use cookies?**

Yes, like many websites, we do use cookies.For further clarification around our cookies, we kindly refer you to our Cookie Policy.
